Guide to the Charles Garside Jr. papers, 1953-1987 MS 421
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VII: Media, 178332
  - Lecture on Renaissance Recording, n.d.; 179020 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Lecture Slides, n.d.; 179021 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - "What is Democracy" Lecture Recording, n.d.; 179022 (Box 9, Folder 38)